{
    "subject": "resource/Kingdom_of_Portugal",
    "predicate": "property/continent",
    "object": "Europe",
    "human_readable": "The Kingdom of Portugal is located in Europe.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9527913928031921,
            "question": "Is Portugal located in Europe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9225240349769592,
            "question": "Where is the Kingdom of Portugal located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.834649920463562,
            "question": "Where geographically is the Kingdom of Portugal found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8139795064926147,
            "question": "Is Portugal a European country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8037646412849426,
            "question": "On which continent is the Kingdom of Portugal situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7655580043792725,
            "question": "Is Portugal an European nation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.627699613571167,
            "question": "What is the geographical location of Portugal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5307690501213074,
            "question": "In which part of the world is Portugal situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40027526021003723,
            "question": "What continent contains Portugal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.282316118478775,
            "question": "To what continent does Portugal belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Kingdom of Portugal is located in Europe.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7814_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What continent contains Portugal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7814_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which part of the world is Portugal situated?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7814_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the geographical location of Portugal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7814_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7814_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7814_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7814_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7814_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7814_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7814_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7814_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7814_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7814_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7814_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThis answer is derived from the information provided across multiple documents, which consistently indicate that Portugal is a country in southwestern Europe, bordering the Atlantic Ocean and Spain. Therefore, the statement \"The Kingdom of Portugal is located in Europe\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}